by H.
Yoo-hoo good morning!
Good morning
And us.
Hey!Mami. Nice to meet you.
I'm excited.
Excited.
This time, I'll be working on everyone's powerful and energetic menu scene, etc.
Motion graphics and more.
I'm going to do a full-body shot again.
And then we're going to shoot the whole body again.
And then we're going to shoot the staff's facial expressions.
and then we shoot the facial expressions of the bustaff.
Finally, I will take a full-body shot with white carving.
Thank you very much for your cooperation today.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Oh no, it's my first time!
Hey Mommy, first time for a MV.
My first real first!
Oh, my God!
Mr. Hara, please take care of me.
I forgot my shoes!
Jump before you dance!
I want to do my best
Let's get started!
covered in green
I'm covered in green
And my clothes are green
Her clothes are green, too.
Asuka, everything might be transparent
She might be green with a green bag, and she might be naked.
Only my face
I'm so nervous to dance solo by myself.
I'll try my best to cover it up with a smile.
What did you think of what I just said?
It's a little nerve-wracking.
This makes me nervous.
But I'll do my best.
Thank you for watching.
Ending Song
Dancing Dancing Dancing
Are you ready?
Kikikuebi day Bari Bari
Hey there We are
Super duper sensibility
The future we envision here
We're just going crazy, casually...
Say hello with you
Yeah yeah yeah baby say hello say hello
You know it's gonna be great
You know it's gonna
Hey baby
I'm a little nervous,
I'm a little nervous, but I'll try not to think too much and have fun.
Thanks for watching:)
My name is Kana Hiramaki. I'm Kana Hiramaki, and I'm looking forward to working with you.
Yes, OK!
Yay!
Yes!
Yes! Yes!
Cute!
Yes!
A little time, a little time, always a little time.
It's simply a song about you and me.
Nanana nananana
Kitchen, kitchen, kitchen, kitchen
I've never done this before.
That's it!
Imagination activity
So much fun!
I always lie down at YURIHIMA's
That's right!
Ever since Asha.
First time you got to sleep in.
Today's hair color is crisp.
It's crisp.
Seino
ด Titans!
Taimi!
, "She's a Kinder soba có một Titan."
estil neither a Titan nor a tierra
Body Chie
Fay
weekend
Enough, enough, enough.
Ears to ears
A little bit more, a little bit more
And here we goSo, I'm going in here.
A moment before power.
I think this is earlier.
Thank you.
The ending is already like this
Thank you very much.
Extra
Yes, eat then.
Mugumogumogumogumogumogumogumogumogumogumogumogumogumogumogumogum
Delicious.
Try it again.
I've never had it before.
LOL!
My first watermelon!
Delicious!
I'm in a bathing suit!
New watermelon!
New argget!
The fourth one?
A lot of watermelons!
I ate a lot.
I'm going to be so hungry!
I'm so happy!
Want some more?
I'll have some!
I want some!
I want to eat it!
I want to eat!
Boxing for the first time! I'll do my best!
First land
Do you know if the first landing is coming?
You! If you do, I'll do it as soon as you do!
Oh, excuse me.
Do I look good?
What? Reading?
Reading.
Do you usually read?
I don't have enough time.
This is what I was reading.
Can I show you?
Read it or watch it?
I showed it to you.
Then let's read it as it is.
Let's read the next one. Let's read next time.
Yes, I'll read it. Turn the page.
Singing laboratory
I'll walk!
I'll be a walker!
Cute!
So cute!
I'm so surprised.
You scared me.
Get in here.
Thank you for watching.
No, no, no. Pre-prepared.
It looks like mom is filming now.
Yes, let's go.
Sparkle! Sparkle!
Advantage camera!
Scurry! Scurrying!
Isn't Mr. Oka filming now?
Here he comes.
Look, he's cute!
He's so cute!
Are you filming? Yes, I'm filming.
I'm filming it! I'm filming all the time!
Diapers!
Don't go, Diaper!
How old are you today?
Four!
Four years old!
You're four?
Mr. Sato said he's four.
I'm 20 years old.
That's amazing.
Were you nervous?
Yeah, I was.
You were so cute.
Hey!
Imaoka-san!
Hey, that wasn't him.
Hey!
Imaoka!
Are you okay?
I'm in the mic room!
Yay!
Kizuna Eye!
Oh! She's so cute!
A little too cute!
Hey, you're so cute!
Are you guys all cutie-doodle-doo?
Yeah!
Yeah!Yay!
What is this song about?
Anyway...
Teebury's
It's full of happy brightness.
I hope fans will remember this song!
Yes!
If you have a child's heart
Anyone can dance
A little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit
Just a little bit.
No?
A little different?
Hmm? Mmm!
Yee!
Hello, director, how's it going?
How's the filming?
Laughing.
Mayka, it's started.
We're going to have a boxing session over here.
Your child looks so cute, like she's dancing.
What are you filming?
Oh! That's it!
It's the one with the overlap.
Like this, like this.
No, no, no. Like this, like this.
No, no, no, no. I did it. I did it.
Well, like this.
Ah!
Oh, here's a picture.
It's cute.
It looks great on you.
Well, let me take a look.
What do you think?
I didn't go through with it.
LOL!
Laughs.
If it's an option...
It's a good dream!
Oh! That's great!
Try it.
Start with your face.
That's great.
That looks strong.
Wow.
Run and you'll catch a tailwind Don't worry, now you can believe in the future
Let it go Don't be afraid
I wanna be a police officer
It's a home day Wake up Wake up
Come play with me
I'm in a good mood, I'm excited
It's just another normal day
Boredom's getting boring, isn't it?
I'm going to fall asleep I've got to go to the mountains
Now we're gonna dance and dance and dance and dance some more
Hey, bleed, you're too sloppy
Someone mumbles, "I'm starving!
It's time to have some fun
That's probably the best thing that ever happened to me.
That's the best thing that ever happened to me.
Thanks for watching!
Say hello, say hello, say hello
Bye bye good bye, good bye
Let's keep saying Hey lady
Thank you for watching!
Wake it up, Wake it up, Shake it up, Do do do do
Wake it up, Wake it up, Shake it up, Do do do do do
OK!
OK! Thank you very much!
In space, nice, Say Yaho!
Say Yaho!
Are you ready?
Yah, Yah, Yah, Yah, Yah!
A few words from here
A little time
With a little time and a little rhythm
Simply my song and your song
nanana number one
A little bit of this, a little bit of that
A little bit of this, a little bit of that, a little bit of magic
My you is cuter than usual
It's so simple, isn't it?
Say hello say hello say hello
Party Party, you're cool, you're cool, you're cool
Hey Ready
Say hello, say hello, say hello
nanana number one
Cute everyday Pappa Party
Yeah you wanna sporty one
nanana number one
Maybe love maybe love
That's all for today's shoot.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Okay, everyone, one, two, three,
Hey! That was magic!
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
Mr. Lippe, what are you wearing?
Why the pajamas?
Why are you my dad?
Why?
Now I'm losing my personality.
It's getting more and more like a music video.
Let's be honest, it's all about selling back and being Ronky.
That's not true.
Kanna, you ate a lot of watermelon.
That's right.
About six slices.
How about six slices?
It'll be bigger, won't it?
Much bigger.
Super duper girl.
Personality Video
Around here
Gummy Lights
I love it!
I'm off!
Yeah!
From here and...